seuscraft.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on November 27, 2013.

Seus Corp Ltd (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates seuscraft.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at seuscraft.com.

**Information Collection And Use**  
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number (“Personal Information”).

**Payment Information**  
When purchasing products from our Site, we ask you to provide us with personally identifiable payment information, including credit card number, expiration date, and CVV number. Your credit card number and CVV number are never stored on our server, but are passed directly to our third-party payment provider. Our third-party payment provider has been audited by a PCI-certified auditor, and is certified to [PCI Service Provider Level 1](http://www.visa.com/splisting/searchGrsp.do?companyNameCriteria=stripe). This is the most stringent level of certification available.

**Security**  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use industry-standard 256-bit encryption to protect your Personal Information and conduct daily malware scans of our site to attempt to ensure the privacy of your information. Remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Log Data**  
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

**Communications**  
If you opt in, we may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in any email we send.

Should you purchase products from us, we may use your Personal Information to contact you with information, questions or updates regarding your order. We may also contact you to provide the opportunity to opt in to aforementioned newsletters, marketing or promotional materials.

**Compliance With Laws**  
Seus Corp Ltd will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Site.

**Business Transactions**  
If Seus Corp Ltd is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred. We will provide notice on this page before your Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. At no point will Seus Corp Ltd duplicate your Personal Information and provide it to a third-party for the purpose of spamming.

**Links To Other Sites**  
Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

Seus Corp Ltd has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**  
Seus Corp Ltd may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:support@seusx.com).
